<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CLI on IC Steve</title>
    <link>https://icsteve.com/en/tags/cli/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CLI on IC Steve</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://icsteve.com/en/tags/cli/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project Goals (tcl-csh-cli)</title>
      <link>https://icsteve.com/en/2021/11/tcl_csh_cli_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icsteve.com/en/2021/11/tcl_csh_cli_2/</guid>
      <description>As a project manager, one very important task is to learn, understand, broadcast the project goal correctly and efficiently. This must be documented and put a place, so that project manager can go through it in the meeting and the team can refer to the document any time.
The solution could be dropbox, sharepoint, onenote, git, ftp, etc.
Goal of &amp;ldquo;tcl-csh-cli&amp;rdquo; Let&amp;rsquo;s look at the goal of &amp;ldquo;tcl-csh-cli&amp;rdquo; project.
Major Goal Create a framework using tcl and csh to handle the complex design requirement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Kick-off (tcl-csh-cli)</title>
      <link>https://icsteve.com/en/2021/11/tcl_csh_cli_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icsteve.com/en/2021/11/tcl_csh_cli_1/</guid>
      <description>This is a project used to demostrate the project management process and also it is my first project which could benefit the IC design community.
I will build a course to finish this project through several months. And the project name is &amp;ldquo;Build Cli with tcl and csh&amp;rdquo;.
The project will be split to several sections in a course to tell some key technology stuff and program management skills.
Project Initialzation First question, how does this project come out?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project technology selection (tcl-csh-cli)</title>
      <link>https://icsteve.com/en/2021/11/tcl_csh_cli_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icsteve.com/en/2021/11/tcl_csh_cli_3/</guid>
      <description>In this post, I would like to talk about my view on technology selection.
When we talk about VLSI CAD (not EDA), most people will think about CS background, coding ability, etc.
But I want to think out of box, as a project manager, I can not just pick option 1 or option 2. It is always good to use SME (Subject Matter Expert) tool. So we may need to group a team with option 1 and option 2 mixture.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
